[
  {
    "question": "Alaska is both the most western and eastern state in the U.S",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Frankenstein is a monster’s name.",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "question": "It is impossible to hum with your nose plugged. :)",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Bill Gates, Steve Jobs, AND Mark Zuckerberg didn’t graduate from college.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Tomatoes are a vegetables.",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Abraham Lincoln was the tallest president.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "question": "There are enough beaches in Australia to visit a new one everyday for 27 years.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "question": "There is at least one pair of identical snowflakes.",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Bananas grow on trees.",
    "Answer": false
  },
  {
    "question": "It snows metal on Venus.",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Thanks for playing!"
  }

]